live.
>> Like I said, welcome brothers and
sisters to another Wednesday question
and answer where we open up with the ten
commandments that God commanded for the
whole world to keep. Brother James,
and God spake all these words, saying, I
am the Lord thy God, which have brought
thee out of the land of Egypt, out of
the house of bondage. Thou shalt have
nor the gods before me. Thou shalt not
make unto thee any graven image or any
likeness of anything that is in heaven
above, or that is in the earth beneath,
or that is in the water under the earth.
Thou shalt not bow down thyself to them,
nor serve them. For I, the Lord thy God,
am a jealous God, visiting the iniquity
of the fathers, upon the children unto
the third and fourth generation of them
that hate me, and showing mercy unto
thousands of them that love me, and keep
my commandments. Thou shalt not take the
name of the Lord thy God in vain, for
the Lord will not hold him guiltless
that taketh his name in vain. Remember
the Sabbath day to keep it holy. Sixth
day shalt thou labor and do all thy
work. But the seventh day is the Sabbath
of the Lord thy God. In it thou shalt
not do any work. Thou nor thy son, nor
thy daughter, thy man's servant, nor thy
maid servant, nor thy cattle, nor thy
stranger that is within thy gates. For
in six days the Lord made heaven and
earth, the sea, and all that in them is,
and rested the seventh day. Wherefore
the Lord blessed the Sabbath day, and
hallowed it. Honor thy father and thy
mother, that thy days may be long upon
the land which the Lord thy God giveth
thee. Thou shalt not kill. Thou shalt
not commit adultery. Thou shalt not
steal. Thou shalt not bear false witness
against thy neighbor. Thou shalt not
covet thy neighbor's house. Thou shalt
not covet thy neighbor's wife, nor is
man's servant, nor is maid servant, nor
as ox, nor is ass, nor anything that is
thy neighbors. I read Exodus 20:es 1-17.
May the Lord add a blessing to the
reading of this word. In Jesus name we
pray. Amen.
>> Amen.
So here on question and answer, you can
ask us a question and we'll answer it
according to the King James Bible. And
if we cannot find the answer, we will
seek further counsel to bring you an
answer at a later time. The questions we
will not answer are the vague as well as
the long scripture questions and
questions of debate. We are not here to
debate. We are here to spread the true
gospel of Jesus. So, please be as direct
as possible with your questions so we
can be as direct as possible with our
answers out of the King James Bible. No
other Bibles or books will be
acknowledged on this program. Also, keep
in mind that this is a live stream, so
feel free to send in your questions that
pertain to everlasting life. We just ask
that you keep them to a two scripture
maximum. Let me introduce you the family
that's on the panel this evening.
Brother Julius.
>> Good evening everybody. Brother Dre,
>> good evening.
>> Brother Jerome, rest in peace. Brother
James,
>> good evening everyone.
>> Sister Deborah,
>> good evening.
>> And we have Sister Casey with us as well
as the guest caller and I'm brother
Cornell. What is our first question of
the show?
>> Yes. Uh there are several held over
questions that will be answered first
before getting into tonight's Q&A. Uh
Kesha Bean Kemp asks, "Can a woman
perform a eulogy?"
>> So, Brother Julius, can a woman perform
a eulogy?
>> That answer is no. She cannot perform a
eulogy. When you are performing a july,
you are in the word of God and you're
standing before the people and you
really are teaching, not just giving a
testimony of somebody's life, but you're
using scripture. That's what the uh
eulogy is for to give scripture uh for
the living. So, the answer is no. Uh
let's let's go to this one script. Let's
go to this script. Let's go to first
Timothy because
uh everything is upside down and out of
order just like there are female pastors
but there's not one in the scriptures.
1 Timothy 2, brother James,
1 Timothy 2
and
verse 11.
You can read, you on your own, read
verse nine, but we really want verse uh
11.
Go ahead, brother.
>> Let the woman learn in silence with all
subjection.
>> Uh-huh.
>> But I suffer not a woman to teach, nor
to usurp authority over the man, but to
be in silence.
>> So that's what the scriptures say.
That's what the scriptures say. Let's go
to The book of Titus.
The book of Titus.
That is right after second Timothy. The
book of Titus
chapter 2. We're going to read verse
three.
And let's look at what the Lord
according to Paul's writing. Go ahead.
>> The age women likewise.
>> Get up there at verse one, brother.
Titus 2 and one. But speak thou the
things which become sound doctrine.
>> The sound doctrine. Skip down to verse
three and go ahead.
>> The aged women likewise, that they be in
behavior as becometh holiness, not false
accusers, not given to much wine,
teachers of good things.
>> Uh-huh. Not to stand behind the pool
pit. Go ahead. that they may teach the
young women to be sober, to love their
husbands, to love their children.
>> What else? The last verse. Go ahead.
>> To be discreet, chase keepers at home,
good, obedient to their own husbands,
that the word of God be not blaspheme.
>> That's all I got, brother Cornell.
>> All right. So, yes, sir. That applies to
whether a body is present or whether
you're doing a memorial also. Right,
brother?
>> That is right.
>> All right. Thank you for that. We hope
that answers your question as we
continue to move on to our next one.
>> Next one. Pauline R wants you to shed
some light on Isaiah 32
13 and 14.
>> All right. Please shed some light on
Isaiah 32 13 and 14. Brother Jerome,
>> let's go read it. And uh when you get it
uh James, go ahead and read.
>> Okay. Isaiah 32:13 and 14 says, "Upon
the land of my people shall come up
thorns and briars. Yay, upon all the
houses of joy in the joyous city,
because the palaces shall be forsaken,
the multitude of the city shall be left,
the forts and towers shall be for dens
forever, a joy of wild asses, a pasture
of flocks.
>> Yeah, this is talking about uh Israel
being disobedient and the Lord is
passing judgment.
Oh, you going to punish the people. So
he punished he punished the people the
children of Judah and Israel and uh even
they children in these modern days which
are us you know we we still suffering
from the punishment even into this day.
Okay. But let's uh let's go to um
chapter five.
The Lord said the land my people shall
come up thorns and briars.
You know,
Lord said he going to destroy his the
land and he going to destroy the people,
scatter them off the land. All that's
talking about his people Israel.
You pick it up at one, read it to uh
seven.
>> Okay. Uh Isaiah 5:1 says, "Now will I
sing to my wellbeloved a song of my
beloved touching his vineyard. My
wellbeloved have a vineyard in a very
fruitful hill."
And he fenced it and gathered out the
stones thereof, and planted it with the
choices vine, and built a tower in the
midst of it, and also made a wine press
therein. And he looked that it should
bring forth grapes, and it brought forth
wild grapes.
>> Yeah. They refused to obey the Lord. Go
ahead.
>> And now, oh inhabitants of Jerusalem and
men of Judah, judge, I pray you be betw
twix me and my vineyard.
What could have been done more to my
vineyard that I have not done in it?
Wherefore, when I looked that it should
bring forth grapes, brought it forth
wild grapes.
>> Mhm.
>> And now go too, I will tell you what I
will do to my vineyard. I will take away
the hedge thereof, and it shall be eaten
up, and break down the wall thereof, and
it shall be trotten down, and I will lay
it waste. It shall not be pruned, nor
digged, but there shall come up briars
and thorns. I will also command the
clouds that they rain no more rain upon
it. For the vineyard of the Lord of
Hosts is the house of Israel and the men
of Judah his pleasant plant. And he
looked for judgment, and behold
oppression, for righteousness, but
behold a crop.
>> Yeah, that's all I got.
All right, thank you for that, brother.
Hope that answered that question as we
move on to our next one.
>> Moving on. Uh Jeffrey Meyers wants you
to explain how Isaiah 55 verse3 applies
to him.
>> All right. So, brother Jeffrey want to
know if that Isaiah 55 and3 applies to
him. And I'm sure you mean others like
mine. But go ahead, brother.
>> Yes, sir. Brother Drake.
>> Uh, let's go to Isaiah 55. We going to
read one and then we'll skip to three.
>> Go ahead, Brother James, when you get
it.
>> Oh, everyone that thirsteth, come ye to
the waters. And he that hath no money,
come ye, buy and eat. Yay, come buy wine
and milk without money and without
price.
>> Right. Well, we talking about a price
here that we were bought with.
And so we'll we'll get into that. Skip
down to verse three and read it,
brother. Go ahead.
>> Incline your ear and come unto me. Hear
and your soul shall live and I will make
an everlasting covenant with you, even
the sure mercies of David.
>> That's right. So we talking about here
incline your ear and come on to me here
and your soul shall live and I will make
an everlasting covenant with you even
the sure mercies of David. Now let's go
to Psalm 89.
Psalm 89. And we're going to read uh
verse one there and we'll skip down to
three. Psalm 89 verse one and then skip
to three.
>> Okay. It says, "I will sing of the
mercies of the Lord forever. With my
mouth will I make known thy faithfulness
to all generations."
>> Yes, sir. Go ahead.
>> Verse three says, "I have made a
covenant with my chosen. I have sworn
unto David, my servant."
>> That's right. So we talking about the
mercies of the Lord and the covenant
with his chosen whom he sworn to David.
Verse four, go ahead.
>> Thy seed will I establish forever and
build up thy throne to all generations.
>> Right now he talking about David's seed
will he establish forever. Now let's go
look at that. Let's go to Acts 13. Now,
Acts 13 and we're going to see how this
applies.
Acts 13 and verse 22.
Read 22 and 23.
>> Okay. Acts 13 and 22 says, "And when he
had removed him, he raised up unto them
David to be their king, to whom also he
gave testimony, and said, I have found
David, the son of Jesse, a man after my
own heart, which shall fulfill all my
will."
>> Mhm. of this man's seed hath God
according to his promise raised unto
Israel a savior Jesus.
>> That's right. So after Saul, the Lord
raised up David and he gave the
testimony that this is David, a man
after God's own heart who will fulfill
all his will. And of this man's seed
hath God according to the promise raised
onto Israel a savior Jesus. Skip down to
verse 32, brother. Go ahead.
And we declare unto you glad tidings,
how that the promises which was made
unto the fathers, God hath fulfilled the
same unto us their children, and that he
hath raised up Jesus again, as it is
also written in the second Psalm, "Thou
art my son, this day have I begotten
thee."
>> Go ahead. Verse 34. And as concerning
that he raised him up from the dead, now
no more to return to corruption. He
said, "On this wise, I will give you the
sure mercies of David."
>> That's right. And that sure mercy is
Christ because in Christ shall all
nations of the earth be blessed. And it
applies to you because you want that
blessing. Even the sure mercies of
David. That's all I got.
>> Yes, sir. Brother Dre. and to be after
God's heart is a beautiful place to go
after.
>> Yes sir, brother.
>> Yes sir. Thank you for that. Hope that
answered their question as we move on to
our next. Moving on. Melon Natural
Journey says, "I have been hearing
people online talking about Jesus is
coming back on September the 22nd, 2025.
Why do people always try to predict
Jesus coming?
Well, when you don't have the true
knowledge of God, it brings forth a lot
of guesses and this is what I think and
what I feel and people lean into their
own understanding. But I know that Rost
Shana began Monday and is still going
until midnight today. So, we see that he
has not come on the 22nd, which is a
couple days ago. And he has all the way
up until midnight tonight. And we can
assure you on this panel that he won't
be coming tonight either. He may come
for a personal individual and put them
to sleep, but as far as coming period,
that won't happen. So, let's go to um
let's go to that Matthew 24 because we
know that Jesus can't come until the
seven trumpet is blown. And we just
celebrated the blowing of the trumpets.
And it's stated in there that at the
seventh trumpet that the Lord will
return. But let's read something prior
to that. Matthew's the 24th chapter and
let's pick it up at verse 15 and then we
going to skip because this also has to
happen before Jesus come. Go ahead.
>> When ye pick up 14, brother, pick it up
in 14 for me. Matthew 24:14 says, "And
this gospel of the kingdom shall be
preached in all the world for a witness
unto all nations, and then shall the end
come."
>> Uh-huh.
>> When ye therefore shall see the
abomination of desolation spoken of by
Daniel the prophet, stand in the holy
place, who so readeth, let him
understand. So we know that the
abomination of desolation, this is the
pope when he moves over into the holy
place which is Jerusalem. That has not
taken place either. But we see in 14 and
this gospel of the kingdom shall be
preached in all the world for a witness.
That's why you have to be somewhere
where you are being taught properly and
the true uncut word of God so that you
will know when the Lord shall return.
Now, once this great tribulation takes
place, the abomination of desolation,
when he standing a holy place, let's see
what's going to happen immediately after
his 3 and 1/2 years of rain. Skip down,
brother, and pick it up at that verse 27
for me. Go ahead.
For as the lightning cometh out of the
east, and shineth even unto the west, so
shall also the coming of the Son of Man
be. Now, we haven't seen that take place
either. The lightning cometh out of the
east and shineth even unto the west. Go
ahead.
>> For whosoever the the carcass is, there
will the eagles be gathered together.
>> Uh-huh. Immediately after the
tribulation of those days shel shall the
sun be darkened and the moon shall not
give her light and the stars shall fall
from heaven and the powers of the
heavens shall be shaken.
>> So after that great tribulation
immediately after then shall the sun be
darkened. The sun is still out there
shine today in fact and it says and the
moon shall not give her light and the
stars shall fall from heaven. This going
to be big news for the world to see. Go
ahead.
>> And then shall appear the sign of the
son of man in heaven. And then shall all
the tribes of the earth mourn, and they
shall see the son of man coming in the
clouds of heaven with power and great
glory.
>> So this is when you shall see the son,
which is Jesus, coming with the clouds
of heaven with power and with great
glory. And so anybody else is saying it
was going to be Monday and it's going to
be today,
that's not true. The book does not back
that up. When you see these things take
place, when you see the lightning
shining from the east to the west, then
so shall you see the coming of the son
of man be. So things must take place
before that happen, but it will not be
today. It's for a time to come in the
future. Anybody else like to add?
All right, we thank you and we hope that
that answers your question as we move
on.
>> Moving on, Latia Lewis asks, "When a
woman's monthly issue falls on the
Sabbath, does she and her family stay
home?"
>> All right. So, when a woman has a
monthly issue and it falls on the
Sabbath,
um, do they have to stay at home? Yes.
Caller.
>> No.
Because this building that we hold
service in ain't nothing holy about it.
It got toilets in it.
Then you go and you buy your groceries.
Women on the line shopping uh uh uh uh
cash ashes.
Some could be on their monthly.
people that uh uh uh prepare the food,
put in the grocery stores in factories
on their monthly. There ain't nothing
clean here. Ain't nothing holy here
because there is no law where all the
people that comes on their monthly or
all the unclean people takes special
precautions.
So no,
Bill is not holy.
Ain't nothing clean about it.
That's all I have to say.
All right, hope that answered your
question as we continue to move on to
our next one.
>> Uh, next one. Kenya V. Hayne says, "I'm
confused. If the father's name is Yhovah
and the son's name is Yahua,
I thought Jehovah was a translation of
Yhovah,
Jesus." What was the father's name in
the Old Testament? and scriptures where
he's talking.
>> All right, they put a little bit in that
question there, but the guest caller
will shed some light.
>> Well, I see why it's confused. You're
confused because you don't read. It is
all in the Bible. Jesus is Jehovah.
Let's go in into uh uh Exodus the 6th
chapter and read verses 2 and three.
Exodus 6 and verse 2 and 3 says, "And
God spake unto Moses and said unto him,
I am the Lord.
And I appeared unto Abraham, unto Isaac,
and unto Jacob, by the name of God
Almighty, but by my name Jehovah, was I
not known to them."
So now there was Jehovah that was
talking to Moses.
But when Jehovah came in the flesh, he
didn't come in his own name.
Came in somebody else's name. He was
given another name. Let's go into
Philippians the 2 chapter.
And we're going to read verses 5-7.
Philippians what chap what chapter was
that again? Philippians chapter 2.
>> Okay. And
>> verse 5-7.
Okay. Philippians 2 verse 5-7 says
>> 5- 11
>> 5- 11. Okay.
>> It says, "Let this mind be in you which
was also in Christ Jesus, who being in
the form of God, thought it not robbery
to be equal with God."
>> Now, now pay attention to this right
quick. He said, "Let this mind be in you
which is in Christ Jesus, who being in
the form of God, thought it not robbery
to be equal with God." When he was under
his name Jehovah, he was God and he was
in the form of God. But go ahead and
read,
>> but made himself of no reputation and
took upon him the form of a servant and
was made in the likeness of men.
>> So now he came in the flesh. That mean
he took upon him the servant the form of
a servant. Scripture should tell you
took upon him the seed of Abraham and he
was made flesh and blood just like men.
Go ahead.
>> And being found in fashion as a man, he
humbled himself and became obedient unto
death, even the death of the cross.
Wherefore God also hath highly exalted
him, and given him a name which is above
every name.
So God,
>> through God the Father, how they exalted
him and given him a name above every
name. And let's see what that name is.
Go ahead.
>> That at the name of Jesus, every knee
should bow of things in heaven and
things in earth and things under the
earth.
And that every tongue should confess
that Jesus Christ is Lord to the glory
of God the Father.
So now at the name so he gave him the
name of Jesus above every name that
every knee shall bow and every tongue
shall confess
that Jesus is Christ
at the glory of the father. So let's see
what name he gave him that's above every
name. Go to St. John the 5th chapter
read verse 43
and 43 says
I am come in my father's name and ye
receive me not. If another man shall
come in his own name him ye will
receive.
>> So now Jesus came in his father's name.
So the father gave him the name above
every name. And what name was that? That
was his own name.
>> Yeah.
>> He didn't come in his name. He came in
his own name. Now, let's look at
something here.
So,
God in the Old Testament talked to Moses
and the prophets.
And let's see
about the father since the uh uh thing
was brought up. Who did he talk to?
Go to John 5 and read verse 37. John 5
and37
John
John 5 and37 says and the father himself
which has sent me borne witness of me.
Ye have neither heard his voice at any
time nor seen his shape.
So now that mean that he said the father
you have never heard his voice at any
time or seen his shape. So let's go back
and see who was talking to Moses there.
Let's go into Exodus the 24th chapter.
We're going to read verse one and then
we're going to skip down and read verse
9 through 12.
>> 9 through uh uh 11.
>> Okay. Uh, Exodus 24:1 says, "And he said
unto Moses, come up unto the Lord, thou
and Aaron, Nadab, and Abu, and 70 of the
elders of Israel, and worship ye a far
off."
>> Go ahead.
>> Verse 9.
Verse 9 says, "Then went up Moses and
Aaron, Naab and Abhu, and 70 of the
elders of Israel, and they saw the God
of Israel. And there was under his feet
as it were a paved work of sapphire
stone. and as it were the body of heaven
in his clearness.
And upon the nobles of the children of
Israel, he laid not his hand, and they
saw God, and did eat and drink.
And the
>> And the Lord said unto Moses, "Come up
to me into the mount, and be there, and
I will give thee tables of stone, and a
law, and commandments which I have
written, that thou mayest teach them."
So now
we saw Moses and 74 people of the elders
of Israel saw God. And we heard Moses
and we heard God tell Moses to come up
here and bring the 74 elders. And then
he heard God say, "Come up here. I'm
going give you actually the ten of the
law, which is the ten commandments."
Now the father the it tell you in St.
John uh uh 5 and37 that ain't nobody
ever seen the father
at any time have heard his voice. So
then, who was this that they saw? Let's
go to the last place. 1 Corinthians 10
and read verses 1-4.
>> Okay. 1 Corinthian 10
verses
1-4 says, "Moreover, brethren, I would
not that ye should be ignorant how that
all our fathers were under the cloud,
and all passed through the sea, and were
all baptized unto Moses in the cloud and
in the sea, and did all eat the same
spiritual meat, and did all drink the
same spiritual drink? For they drank of
that spiritual rock that followed them,
and that rock was Christ.
>> So that God of the Old Testament, which
is Jehovah, Yahweh,
is also Jesus.
And the name of the fathers,
old and new, as far as we concerned, is
Jesus. Why? Because Jesus said he come
in the name of the father. So the God of
the Old Testament, we never dealt with
the father at any time. I heard his
voice. That's why Jesus say, "I am alpha
and omega, the beginning and the end,
the first and the last. I'm the god that
dealt with you the beginning and I'm
going to be the god that deal with you
deal with you in the end. And when the
father come down, there will be no such
species as man. Everybody will come
under the heading of God.
The only God we ever dealt with was
Jesus. You ain't never dealt with the
father.
That's all I have to say.
>> All right. Thank you for that. And thank
you for that good question. As we
continue to move on to our next one,
>> moving on. Uh, Timeout Houston says,
"Did God give Abraham the same laws,
statutes, and commandments as Moses or
Mount Si, or were they different?
Just like we don't keep the exact same
laws they kept in Moses time.
>> All right. So, brother Julius, what
about these laws?
>> You're on mute, Julius.
>> Thank you, brother.
>> You're welcome.
>> This was This question came in last
week. Just put a little bit of a spin on
it. The answer remains the same.
Did God give Abraham the same law,
statutes, and commandments as Moses?
Moses was the one that wrote about
Abraham.
Let's go. Let's go to Genesis chapter
two, James. Let's go to Genesis chapter
2 because for some reason people think
that God changes when it comes to his
law, statutes, and his commandments.
Genesis chapter 2 and verse 7.
Since someone since uh uh um time
Houston is saying since uh just like we
don't keep the exact s same laws as they
kept in Moses. Moses was the one that
gave you the ten commandments which
identify what sin is.
Sin is a transgression of the law. So
the law gave you the ten commandments
for the whole world for the whole world
to keep including Abraham. The wages of
sin is death. Let me show you. Because
we still die today. Why? Because sin is
still in the world. Because people still
break the commandments of God. Because
Adam bought sin into this right here.
Let's go back before Abraham.
Genesis 2 and 7. Go ahead, James.
>> And the Lord God formed man of the dust
of the ground and breathed into his
nostrils the breath of life, and man
became a living soul. So on the own you
read the I want to get to the meat of
this right here. The Lord commanded the
man. Let's skip down of the tree that he
can eat from and the tree that he shall
not eat of. And this tree of life is
Jesus. This tree of the knowledge of
good and evil is Satan the devil. Go
ahead at verse 16. Uh 17 uh um uh yeah
16. Go ahead, brother. And the Lord God
commanded the man, saying, of every tree
of the garden, thou mayest freely eat.
But of the tree of the knowledge of good
and evil, thou shalt not eat of it. For
in the day that thou eatest thereof,
thou shalt surely die.
>> So this is death being introduced before
man sin. Now man didn't listen. He broke
the commandment. Go to Genesis 3 and 19.
Let's look at the man die and where he
go from that day to this one.
Verse 19. In the sweat of thy face shalt
thou eat bread till thou return unto the
ground. For out of it was thou taken for
dust thou art and unto dust shalt thou
return. That means you die. Everybody
and everything die, sisters and brother,
because somebody broke the commandment
by one man sin into the world. That's
Adam and death pass upon all men. Let's
go one last place
cuz Psalm 119, go back on last week's
and read the same scriptures. What must
I do in Matthew 19? Keep the
commandments to have eternal life. Keep
the commandments.
Psalm 119 and just give me one verse,
brother. 142.
>> Okay. 119 and 142 says,
>> Yes, sir. Thy righteousness is an
everlasting righteousness, and thy law
is the truth.
>> So therefore, Jesus told you from
everlasting to everlasting. He's God,
and that his righteousness is from
everlasting. He's a right God. So
therefore, I went there to show you that
God's commandments, just like he told
you in the beginning, he told you in
Exodus, he told you all through the
book, and then he told you in Revelation
22 and 14. Revelation 22:14,
last place.
>> Okay,
>> let's see if the commandments are still
good.
>> Blessed are they that do his
commandments
>> that they may have right to the tree of
life.
>> Yes.
>> And may enter in through the gates into
the city.
>> So now you keep the commandments, you
have eternal life. Abraham kept the
commandments. Moses kept the
commandments. All the prophets, the
servants of God, true servants of God,
the apostles except they kept the
commandments, sisters and brothers,
because the commandments are from
everlasting to everlasting. He just gave
it to Israel on Mount Si, but they
always existed. The devil broke the
commandment and he got kicked out of
heaven. So therefore, I don't know where
this is coming from. Just like we don't
keep the exact same laws they kept in
Moses laws. If you steal, you going to
jail.
Same thing. Cuz the wages of sin is
death from beginning to the end. So the
answer don't change.
>> Yeah.
>> Let's do good.
>> Yeah. Can we read one verse out there?
Leviticus 24.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Leviticus 24 and 22. When you get there,
Brother Jane,
>> it says, "Ye shall have one manner of
law as well for the stranger as for one
of your own country. For I am the Lord
your God."
>> Yes, sir. One law for the stranger, one
law for those among Israel.
among among Israel, among the Hemites,
everybody's under one law. Sister and
brothers, guess calling,
>> let me read one thing that uh God told
Moses
that when he bring Israel back to the
land, let's see what law they going to
keep.
That's Deuteronomy 30 and verse 8.
>> Yes, sir.
Deuteronomy 30 and verse 8 says,
>> "And thou shalt return and obey the
voice of the Lord and do all his
commandments which I command thee this
day."
>> What day?
>> This day.
>> Yeah.
>> That mean nothing. That's all I have to
say.
>> Yeah. All right.
>> Thank you.
>> Get that answer. Your question is we
move on to our next one with the time
check.
>> Yes, the time is 8:09.
Uh, Lady J asks in Leviticus 11
10 and 11. Is God only speaking of the
fish of the sea? I take sea supplements
and I wanted to make sure if it was okay
to take.
>> All right. Uh, that's a good question,
brother Dre, cuz this sea moss been
sweeping all across the channels. So,
what you say, brother?
>> Yeah, sea moss is not flesh. It's a it's
a algae or a plant, seaweed,
>> something along that line. But let's go
to Leviticus
11 and start at verse 9. Leviticus 11,
start at verse 9. Brother James, when
you get it, go ahead.
These shall ye eat of all that are in
the waters. Whatsoever hath fins and
scales in the waters, in the seas, and
in the rivers, them shall ye eat.
>> So we talking about whatever is in the
waters that have fins and scales,
those shall we eat. Go ahead.
and all that have not fins and scales in
the seas and in the rivers of all that
move in the waters and of any living
thing which is in the waters they shall
be an abomination unto you.
>> Read verse 11.
>> They shall be even an abomination unto
you. Ye shall not eat of their flesh,
but ye shall have their but ye shall
have their carcasses an abomination.
>> Notice it said, "Ye shall not eat of
their flesh."
>> You're talking about flesh. And when you
you get a crab or whatever, they peel
the crab away and they eat the flesh.
They peel the shell off of the shellfish
and they eat the flesh that's in it. It
is unclean onto you. But as far as um
seaoss, seaoss is a plant in the water
that is a uh a weed or an algae.
Book don't say nothing about you can't
eat that. That's all I got.
>> All right. Thank you for that, brother.
We move on to our next question.
>> Next question. V alert as in Revelation
7 verse5.
Can you please explain the meaning of
the three ribs?
>> All right, let's go to that Revelation
7.
Revelation 7
and let's pick it up at that verse five
and then the guest caller will take it
from there.
Okay. Revelation 7 and5 says,
"Of the tribe of Judah were sealed
12,000 of the tribe of Reuben."
>> They gave the wrong scripture,
>> right? I was thinking it was Daniel 7
and5.
>> Yeah, that's correct.
>> Okay.
Daniel
7 and5 said, "And behold, another beast,
a second like to a bear, and it raised
up itself on one side, and it had three
ribs in the mouth of it between the
teeth of it, and they said, "Thus unto
it, arise, devour much flesh."
So, you want to know what the three ribs
stand for? I don't have a clue.
That's all I have to say.
>> All right. Well, we were glad to catch
where you meant to go instead of what's
on paper. All right. We're going to
continue to move on to our next one.
>> Moving on. Robert Dol uh wants you to uh
ex Robert Doch wants you to explain Luke
6 verse 26.
>> All right. Luke 6 and verse 26. Brother
Julius,
>> go ahead, brother James. Luke 6 and
verse 26. This is Jesus when he's
speaking. You can read the same thing in
Matthew 5, Matthew the 5th chapter when
Jesus was with his disciples and the
multitudes came out.
Read that verse. Uh instead, let's start
at uh verse read 26. Go ahead, brother.
Woe unto you when all men shall speak
well of you. For so did their fathers to
the false prophets.
>> Now this whole chapter is about uh Jesus
ministering to his disciples and to the
multitude.
Woe unto you when men but uh war to you
when all men shall speak well of you.
You know, like they do about some a lot
of the false prophets and everything.
They speak well about they love the
false prophet. Oh, he's a true man of
God. Woe unto you. They and they speak
well of these people. For so did their
father to the prophets. Check this out
though. Let's back up and let's read
verse 22 because this is a comparison
chapter. Woes and blessings. Now let's
look at the blessings at verse 22.
Blessed are ye when men shall hate you.
>> But we just read, born to you when all
men speak well of you.
>> But then look at this right here.
Blessed are ye when men shall hate you.
Why?
>> And when they shall separate you from
their company,
>> and shall reproach you and cast out your
name as evil for the son of man's sake.
So you we we preach the gospel in the
Israel of God. And a lot of people don't
agree. A lot of people don't like us. We
get sometime nasty letters from from
big- time preachers.
Just like the scripture says, you're
blessed because you telling the truth.
You're telling to keep the Sabbath day,
to keep the feast of the Lord, to keep
God's dietary law, to keep his
commandments. But we're blessed in God's
eyes. But then verse 26 says, "Woe unto
you when all men shall speak well of
you." Because people, the book says,
"People we love lies. Speak uh
flattering things to us. Tell us easy
things. Tell us God love everybody. No
matter what you are, what who you are
and what you've done. Woe unto you
because your home will be the lake of
fire." So this is a comparison
scriptures chapter. The whole chapter is
comparison of scriptures. The Lord is
showing you how to conduct yourselves,
how to behave yourself, and when people
don't like you for the truth sake, then
you're blessed. But when everybody love
you for falsehood and lies, woe unto
you. That's what this is all about. I
hope that helped.
>> Amen.
>> Yes, sir. If you are out of order,
repent and turn from your ways.
All right, we're going to move on to our
next question.
>> Moving on. Uh, Little Finger says, "As
an Israelite,
how do you overcome working in a hostile
work environment? Can you give me some
helpful scriptures to cope? I can't quit
my job."
>> Okay, there's a lot of um scriptures
that we can give and we'll open it up to
the panel as well. But since you can't
quit your job, but you are in a hostile
working environment, good place to
practice being slow to speak and quick
to hear would be at that place. But
let's go into First Thessalonians the
5th chapter. 1 Thessalonians 5.
And we get that first Thessalonians 5. I
want you to pick it up, brother, at that
verse 15 for me.
>> Okay. 1 Thessalonians 5:15 says, "See
that none render evil for evil unto any
man, but ever follow that which is good
both among yourselves and to all men."
>> Rejoice ever more.
Pray without ceasing.
>> And that is the key to pray without
ceasing, too. Because sometime when
you're in a hostile work environment,
sometimes revenge, the desire to do
that. But the Lord say vengeance is his.
So keep praying because the Lord see
your situation. Turn over to Philippians
4. Philippians the 4th chapter. And when
you get there, let's pick it up at that
verse four and then we're going to skip.
Philippians 4
and verse
4 and then we going to skip. Philippians
4 and 4. Where brother?
>> Rejoice in the Lord always. And again I
say rejoice.
>> Mhm.
>> Let your moderation be known unto all
men. The Lord is at hand.
>> Yeah. Go ahead. I want that. Six. Read
six and seven.
>> Be careful for nothing. But in
everything by prayer and supplication
with thanksgiving, let your requests be
made known unto God.
>> So that goes back to that praying
without ceasing and praying to God. And
sometimes you have to pray for either
those that's giving you a hard time to
be removed or even pray for, you know, a
change of department or something to
kind of be of help to you. And verse
seven, go ahead. And the peace of God
which passes all understanding shall
keep your hearts and minds through
Christ Jesus.
>> Last verse, last book, Ephesians 6.
Because this is what you have to put on
regardless. And everybody who has some
word of God, this is what we are all
required to put on. Ephesians 6, read
verse 10
through 12.
>> Okay.
>> Go ahead. Just pick it up at 10 and
read. Go ahead.
>> Finally, my brethren, be strong in the
Lord and in the power of his might.
>> Yep.
>> Put on the whole armor of God, that ye
may be able to stand against the ws of
the devil.
For we wrestle not against flesh and
blood, but against principalities,
against powers, against the rulers of
darkness of this world, against
spiritual wickedness in high places.
>> Yep. Skip down and uh pick it up at
verse uh 16. Above
all, take the shield of faith, wherewith
ye shall be able to quench all the fiery
darts of the wicked.
>> Sometimes when it's hostile there, hey,
you got to have on that shield of faith
to be able to deal and uh just make sure
that you're not the one a part of the
hostility, but that is incoming only. Uh
to the panel, anybody else want to add?
Cornell, I have one one one verse, one
chapter, uh, one book. Romans 12 and 18.
>> That's right. Come on, Julius.
>> Romans 12:18. I've been there and it
works.
>> Yes, it does.
>> Everything that you said was good.
Romans 12:18, James,
>> it says, "If it be possible, as much as
lith in you, live peaceibly with all
men."
>> How you do that? And sometimes you got
to know when to get out of the way and
avoid them.
>> You know, you be you be an ambassador
for Christ as much as lies within you
and you live peacefully and God give to
give you the victory. Like Cornell say,
as long as you are not part of the
hostility because sometime a harsh word
can bring forth hostility,
>> but a soft answer turneth away wrath.
That's all I got. And and actually
Julius, if you if you even add 21, be
not overcome with evil, but overcome
evil with good.
>> That's something that hostility is that
evil spirit could be behind that person
and you just have to overcome.
>> Yeah. Just
>> Yeah. And just keep praying. And hey, if
you serving God with all your heart, you
the apple of his eye and everybody that
mess with you going to have a problem
anyway sooner or later.
>> And if you behave yourself correctly,
you just might become the priest of that
department.
>> Yep.
>> All right. I hope that answered your
question there. As we continue to move
on to our next one,
>> moving on. Uh Liz's question is similar
to a question that was asked last week
about Israelites
and other nations teaching. She says,
"Can a Gentile teach a lesson?
If they are able to teach, can they
teach Israelites or other Gentiles?"
>> All right, guest caller regarding the
Gentile teaching.
Truth of the matter is
according to the scripture I don't see
one Gentile in there teaching nobody but
all but of course Paul is the apostles
to the Gentiles
and he went and he set churches up and
he had and some of the people he set
over the Gentiles was somebody was other
Gentiles. Let's go to Romans 16 and read
verse 3-5.
Romans 16:es
3-5
says
it says greet Priscilla and Aquilla my
helpers in Christ Jesus
who have for my life laid down their own
necks unto whom not only I give thanks
but also all the churches of the
Gentiles.
Likewise greet the church that is in
their house. Salute my wellbeloved
aphenotus who is the first fruits of
Aaya unto Christ.
>> Do not the gentile have churches in the
house and you have gentile teaching
gentile. Go to 1 Corinthians uh uh the
16th chapter and read verse two.
>> Six 16 and2 says, "Upon the first day of
the week, let every one of you lay by
him in store as God has prospered him
that there be no gatherings when I
come."
And when I
>> Yes, that was 16 and two.
Yeah.
I wanted to see where this guy had a
church in his house, too. I tell you,
let's go to Colossians 4:15.
>> Colossians 4
and 15.
It says Colossians 4:15 says, "Solute
the brethren which are in Leodysia and
Nymph and the church which is in his ha
in his house."
Now this is and this is a gentile. He
have a church in his house. That mean
somebody got to be teaching. These are
Gentiles teaching Gentiles. Now let's go
to Titus 1 chapter read verses 4-7
because Paul
said uh uh uh uh you know had them set
up church excuse me go ahead and read
>> okay and that was
>> Titus 1 4-7
>> okay it says to Titus my own son after
the common faith faith, grace, mercy,
and peace from God the Father, and the
Lord Jesus Christ our Savior.
For this for this cause left I thee init
that thou should have set in order the
things that are wanting and ordained
elders in every city as I has as I had
appointed thee.
And if any be blameless,
>> go ahead. the husband of one wife,
having faithful children, not accursed,
of riot, or unruly.
For a bishop must be blameless, as a
steward of God, not self-willed, not
soon angry, not given to whine, no
striker, not given to filthy lucr.
Now, Titus was was a gentile and these
churches he's setting up and putting in
order according to Paul's commandments
are Gentiles. These are Gentiles
teaching Gentiles.
So now,
what happened? 70 AD, the Lord had Judah
taken
and all the Israelites, the Jews were
scattered throughout the Mediterranean.
and from there all the way
all over the world. So now
Israel was scattered, not the Gentiles.
Israel lost sight on himself for a
moment. Not the Gentile. So look at all
of these Gentiles that Paul
Corinthians, the Romans, the Colossians,
the Galatians,
Thessalonians,
all and the Ephesians, Ephesus, all of
these were Gentiles, all these people
Paul taught. But what happened was when
Israel, Judah was taken down in 7 AD,
all Israelite was scattered.
And so, but nobody put the Gentiles
in captivity. Nobody. So, why is it then
that we have the Gentiles teaching now
they teaching that Christ died on Good
Friday and rose Easter Sunday morning.
Christ is born on the 25th day of
December.
Sunday, the first day of the week, is
the Christian Sabbath day. People
are going to be raptured off to heaven.
What happened to all these people that
Paul taught better?
All these Gentiles. What happened to all
that knowledge?
Maybe God had a reason for making sure
that Gentiles
did not teach Israelites especially and
not teach Gentiles without tutors from
Israel
because all of these things uh come from
Israel. Let me show you. They teach
about going to heaven. Go to Isaiah the
14th chapter and start reading at verse
12 and let's see who want to go to
heaven.
Okay.
Isaiah 14 starting at verse 12. It says,
"How art thou fallen from heaven, oh
Lucifer, son of the morning? How art th
How art thou cut down to the ground
which didest weaken the nations?"
>> For thou hast said in thine heart, I
will ascend into heaven. I will exalt my
I will exalt my throne above the stars
of God. I will sit also upon the mount
of the congregation and the sides of the
north. I will ascend above the heights
of the clouds. I will be like the most
high.
Yet
>> now this is Satan. This is Satan and
devil talking, ain't it?
>> Yes, it is.
>> What did he say? He's going back. He's
going to heaven. Ain't that correct?
>> Yes.
Now you go to people have funeral that
has been taught by the gentile. They
said, "Well, this is not sister Sarah
here in the in the box. This is just a
shell. She have made a homecoming. She's
in heaven looking down on you, smiling.
Who will make a homecoming if they go
back to heaven?"
>> Satan.
>> Satan. The devil. So this doctrine that
we call Christianity right now is Satan
doctrine. this devil doctorate.
>> So as soon as Israel was taken out of
the picture, the preach of God was
removed,
the same scripture and gospel fell into
the hand of the Gentile. And look what
we have now.
The doctrine of devils under the name of
Christianity. And I see now why God
didn't let Gentiles teach Israel.
Because as soon as the priest was out of
the way, the Gentiles went to back went
back to what he
is used to doing. And let's go and look
at that. 1 Corinthian the 10th chapter
and read verse 20 and 21.
1 Corinthian the 10th chapter
and verse 20 and 21 says, "But I say
that the things which the Gentiles
sacrifice, they sacrifice to devils and
not to God. And I would
>> to devils and not to gods to God."
>> Next verse.
>> And I would not that ye should have
fellowship with devils. Ye cannot drink
the cup of the Lord and the cup of
devils. Ye cannot be partakers of the
Lord's table and of the table of devils.
Well, you have a way to just Well, we
don't we don't uh uh uh uh sacrifice the
devil. Then who is it that told you you
they want to go to heaven?
>> We got no Satan the devil. We ain't got
no scripture in this Bible that said
that a Gentile can teach Israelites. But
we see where Paul set Gentiles over
Gentiles. He set up Gentiles churches.
But when we got taken out of the
picture, the Gentile reverted back to
what he was doing before he was taught
by the priests and that is sacrificing
the devil. That's all I have to say
about it.
>> All right. Hope that answered your
question there. As we continue to move
on, I believe we moving on into new
territory.
Uh yes, we are now into tonight's Q&A
for Wednesday, September the 24th, 2025.
Shaquila Au jobi says in Matthew 25
verse 23. We all hope to hear those
words one day.
He says, "It makes me wonder, can
someone pursue what they believe is
God's calling but miss their true
purpose?
How can we truly know our purpose?"
>> Matthew 25 and 23. Let's go there first
and let's read that, brother. And then
let's open it up.
to the panel
>> because
um this is a good thing to hear coming
from the Lord too. Go ahead, brother.
His lord said unto him, well done, good
and faithful servant. Thou has been
faithful over a few things. I will make
thee ruler over many things. Enter thou
into the joy of the Lord.
So he wants to know about his own
personal calling. I mean
get get this report here. He in good
shape.
>> Yeah. He says, "Can someone pursue what
they believe is God's calling but miss
their true purpose?" And then he says,
"How can we truly know our purpose?"
Hey,
>> God's purpose is first. Go ahead.
That's what your purpose is to
practice God's purpose.
>> That's right.
>> And that's read his gospel, keep his
commandments,
and do what he say. Everybody want to be
special.
And God told you, let me tell you what
you got to do. And this is what you be
concerned about. Let's go to Matthews
the 19th chapter.
>> Yes, sir.
And let's see what Jesus, this young man
asked Jesus a question.
>> Verse 16.
>> Uhhuh. 19 and 16.
>> Go ahead.
>> It says, "And behold, one came and said
unto him, good master, what good thing
shall I do that I may have eternal
life?"
And he said unto him, "Why callst thou
me good? There is none good but one that
is God. But if thou will enter into
life, keep the commandments.
>> So
if you want to get eternal life, keep
the commandments. That is your purpose.
Now let's go to Ecclesiastes the 12th
chapter.
Ecclesiastes chapter 12.
>> Mhm.
I think we're 13 or somewhere where you
>> 13 and 14.
>> Yeah, 123 and 14. Read it.
>> Let us hear the conclusion of the whole
matter. Fear God and keep his
commandments for this is the whole duty
of man.
>> That is what?
>> The whole duty of man.
>> Go ahead. For God shall bring every work
into judgment with every secret thing,
whether it be good or whether it be
evil.
>> So your purpose is to fear God and keep
his commandments. And if the Lord has
something more he wants you to do, he
will direct you.
But if you don't fear God and keep his
commandments, you have another purpose,
and that's the lake of fire. That's all
I got to say.
>> All right. Hope that answered your
question there. Next one, Deborah.
>> Next one. Lu Cox asks, "What does the
Bible really mean
by honor your father and mother?" Some
of my family member, some of my family
think it means obeying and caring for
parents fully even as an adult. But I
want to know what the scripture says.
>> All right. Open to the panel.
>> What is the meaning of
>> uh honor thy mother and thy father?
>> Yeah. What does the Bible really mean
when they when it says honor your father
and mother?
>> Obey perspective. Go ahead guess caller.
Let's go in Exodus uh uh uh uh
20th chapter and read.
Okay.
Exodus 20 and 12 says, "Honor thy father
and thy mother that thy days may be long
upon the land which the Lord thy God
giveth thee."
>> Thou shalt not kill. Thou shalt not
commit adultery. Thou shalt not steal.
>> Honor thy father, thy mother, that thy
days might be long on earth. And then
why is it somebody can get it up?
Anybody that's uh uh uh
uh you know like
abuse their father or mother or
whatever.
Uh will you say um where you say it's a
gift? 15 15 Matthew 15.
>> What does it say?
>> Matthew 15 and4.
>> Okay. Matthew 15 and4 says,
"For God commanded, saying, "Honor thy
father and mother, and he that cursseth
father or mother, let him die the
death."
>> That's what I'm looking at right there.
Honor don't mean look if they need to be
taken care of then you should do that.
But honor is that you don't be cursing
them and you don't be disrespecting them
cuz they are your mother and your
father. Even if a father ran off and
he's your father and haven't done
nothing to you, you still not supposed
to do that. Where he say if you if you
curse your father a mother die to death
is any more to that?
>> Yes. It says, "But ye say, whosoever
shall say to his father or his mother,
it is a gift. By whatsoever thou
mightest be profited by me,
and honor not his father or his mother,
he shall be free. Thus have ye made the
commandment of God of none effect by
your tradition."
So to honor him is not to push him
around, not to assault him, not to curse
at him, and not to respect him,
disrespect them.
>> Can we Can we go to Oh, go ahead, guest
call. I'm sorry.
>> Go read the scripture.
>> Let's go to Ephesians the 6th chapter.
>> Yes, sir. Dre.
>> Ephesians 6
and pick it up from 1 to three.
>> Okay. Ephesians 6:es
1-3 says, "Children, obey your parents
in the Lord, for this is right.
>> Honor thy father and mother, which is
the first commandment with promise,
>> that it may be well with thee, and thou
mayest live long on the earth."
>> That's right. That commandment got
promise. He's got long life,
>> you know.
>> And verse four, read verse four.
>> And ye fathers, provoke not your
children to wrath, but bring them up in
the nurture and admonition of the Lord.
>> Okay.
>> Yep. That's right, Dre. Cuz that even at
verse two where you read where you had
him read where it say, "Honor thy father
and thy mother," which is the first
commandment with promises. That bags up
that Exodus 12 that you read, James.
>> Mhm. Yes, it does.
>> Yep. So, all right. So, we hope that
that start to set you on the right
track. Guest call them.
>> Yes. So, to honor your mother and your
fathers, not to curse them, not to push
them around, not to beat them, not to
disrespect them.
>> That's right.
>> Not to try and and and uh if you have to
take care of them, if so be and the Lord
bless you to be able to take care of
your mother and your father, then you do
it. But then you don't treat them like
children because you taking care of them
because they got you to where you were
when you was a child.
>> That's right.
>> Respect all times.
>> Yeah. That's right. Absolutely. Give
them the respect cuz uh don't want to
mistreat your parents and then you end
up reaping what you sow and your kids
get you. So should do what's right. All
right. Next question.
Next question. Christy Watson asks,
"What is grace?"
>> Free gift.
>> Yes, it is
>> unearned
blood of Jesus. His his death on the
cross.
Anybody else?
Go ahead.
>> You got Ephesians 2. You got Ephesians
uh 2 and8.
>> Go read it.
>> For by grace are ye saved through faith
and not of yourselves. It is the gift of
God.
>> Yeah.
>> And and that is it. We didn't do nothing
for God, for Jesus to come and die for
us.
>> Oh,
>> because if he had not if he had not died
for us, then we would be cut off. But I
want to throw something in here because
people saying that you ain't under the
law, but you under grace. Let's go into
Hebrews the 10th chapter and look at
something here.
>> Okay.
Hebrews 10 and1 and then we going to
skip.
>> Okay. Hebrews 10 and1 says, "For the law
having a shadow of good things to come
and not the very image of the things can
never with those sacrifices which they
offered year by year continually make
the comers there unto perfect."
So now that law could not help you. Why?
Skip down and read. Start at verse four.
Go ahead.
For it is not possible that the blood of
bulls and of goats should take away
sins.
>> So that so you was under the law of
animal sacrifice. They couldn't take
away sin. So then Jesus had to come and
and give it back. Go ahead.
Wherefore when he cometh into the world,
he saith, Sacrifice and offering thou
wouldest not, but a body hast thou
prepared me.
>> Go ahead.
>> And burnt offerings and sacrifices for
sin, thou has had no pleasure.
Then said I, Lo, I come in the volume of
the book, it is written of me to do thy
will, oh God.
Now skip down to verse 10 to show you
why this body he needed a body.
>> By the which wi by the which will we are
sanctified through the offering of the
body of Christ once for all.
[Music]
and and every priest stand I'm sorry and
every priest standed daily ministering
and offering oftent times the same
sacrifices which can never take away
sins.
But this man, after he had offered one
sacrifice for sins forever, sat down on
the right hand of God,
from henceforth, expecting till his
enemies be made his foottool.
Now he came and he gave you back what
Adam took away from you
and that is a chance become
your mother and God. That was a free
gift. Ain't nothing that you did that uh
uh uh uh that man did that God should
come and die for him.
So grace is a free gift. That mean that
the Lord came and gave you something
that Adam took away from you. Let's look
at 1 Corinthians 15th chapter right
quick.
Okay,
>> let's see where we want to start it at.
>> First Corinthians 15
start at 21. See what it sounds like.
>> Okay. 1 Corinthians 15 and 21 says, "For
since by man came death, by man came
also the resurrection of the dead."
>> Uhhuh. For as in Adam all die, even so
in Christ shall all be made alive,
but every man in his own order, Christ
the first fruits, afterward they that
are Christ at his coming.
So now
Adam took your immortality away from you
and Jesus came and gave it back to you
and you didn't do nothing. Man didn't do
nothing that he could say to God,
I have worked for this,
>> right?
>> But once you get that gift, you have to
work to keep it. It was a free gift. You
got something that you didn't deserve.
>> That's all I have to say.
>> Yep. Free gift. Paul said, "I do not
frustrate the grace of God." Uhuh.
All right.
>> Mean simple as that.
>> Yep. All right. Hope that answered your
question there, Sister Deborah. Next.
>> Next question. Jacob Israel asks, "Can
you break down Isaiah 14
28-31?"
Isaiah, let's go to that Isaiah 14.
>> And when you get there, brother, we're
going to pick it up at that verse 28.
Isaiah 14. And let's pick it up at that
verse 28.
Go ahead, brother.
>> In the year that King Ahaz died was this
burden.
Rejoice not thou hold Palestina, because
the rod of him that smokeote thee is
broken. For out of the serpent's root
shall come forth a cockatrice, and his
fruit shall be a fiery flying serpent.
And the firstborn of the poor shall
feed, and the needy shall lie down in
safety, and I will kill thy root with
famine, and he shall slay thy remnant.
Howl, O gate. Cry, O city, thou, whole
Palestina, art dissolved. For thou shalt
come from the north a smoke, and none
shall be alone in his appointed times.
>> All right. So, let's open it up to the
panel.
>> All it's talking about is when the
Lord's going to come and he is going to
take down
Assyria. and the people that took down
Egypt, Israel. Back up to verse 24.
>> Okay.
>> Yes, sir. That's start at verse 24.
>> Verse 24 says, "The Lord of hosts has
sworn, saying, Surely as I have thought,
so shall it come to pass. And as I have
purposed, so shall it stand." that I
will break the Assyrian in my land, and
upon my mountains tread upon tread him
upon underfoot, then shall his yoke
depart from off them, and his burden
depart from off their shoulders.
Read some more.
>> Oh, this is the purpose that is purposed
upon the whole earth. And this is the
hand that is stretched out upon all the
nations.
>> For the L for the Lord of hosts has
purposed, and who shall disanol it? And
his hand is stretched out, and who shall
turn it back?
>> Just like the Lord the Lord's going to
do to Assyria, he going to do to all
nations. He going to take all of these
nations down for what they did with
Israel. It sounds all uh uh uh talking
about cockat trash and all, but it's
really coming down to one thing. The
Lord going to come and he going to take
out the nation for what they did to his
people.
>> Yeah.
>> The future prophecy
>> and that's all it is.
>> That's all is Palestine.
Everybody in that area
>> and everybody over there is guilty. You
got the that call themselves
Jews in the land of Palestine. Then you
got the the Israelites, the Arabs.
They are also occupying
part of Palestine. All these people over
there are in our land. And the Lord
said, "I'm going to deal with you when I
come back." Let's see what what did he
say that the uh
[Music]
when he said that the uh uh they taking
my silver and my gold and put in their
temple of the children of Israel.
Have they sold to the Grecian?
>> Yep.
>> Yeah. Joel, I think
>> is it Joel? I
>> think so.
>> Talking about the same thing here.
Let's see. Joel 3.
>> Uh-huh. Well, this is when the Lord said
when he going to return Israel. Look
what he going to do. Start at 3 and 1.
>> Okay.
>> 3 and one. Joel Joel 3:1 says, "For
behold, in those days and in that time
will I when I shall bring again the
captivity of Judah and Jerusalem, I will
also gather all nations and will bring
them down into the valley of Jehoshaphat
and will plead with them."
>> All nations. And he going to do what?
and will plead with them there for my
people and for my heritage Israel whom
they have scattered among the nations
and parted my land.
And they have cast and they have cast
lots for my people and have given a boy
for an harlot and sold a girl for wine
that they might drink.
>> Go ahead. You see what he done? He told
me you you know you sold my people. You
taking my land and my gold, and now
you're trading uh daughters off for wine
and and sons off for prostitutes. Go
ahead.
>> Yay. And what have ye to do with me, O
Tyre and Zidon, and all the coast of
Palestine? Will ye render me a
recompense?
>> Then we got back to Palestine again,
didn't we?
>> Yes, sir.
>> Will you render me a repayment? Go ahead
and read. And if ye recompense me
swiftly, speedily, will I return your
recompense upon your own head,
>> because you have because ye have taken
my silver and my gold, and have carried
into your temples my goodly, pleasant
things.
>> Uhhuh.
>> The children also of Judah, and the
children of Jerusalem have ye sold unto
the Grecians, that he might remove them
far from their border.
So this is so the Lord is is letting you
know, you know, look what you've done.
All of you, all the Palestinian, all you
nation, and I am going to uh uh deal
with you. What verse are you?
>> That was verse six.
>> Well, we going to skip now to verse N.
See what the Lord said.
>> Proclaim ye this among the Gentiles.
Prepare war. Wake up the mighty men. Let
all the men of war draw near. Let them
come up. Beat your plowshares into
swords, and your prun hooks into spears.
Let the weak say, I am strong. Go ahead.
>> Assemble yourselves, and come all ye
heathen, and gather yourselves together
round about thither, cuz thy mighty ones
to come down, oh Lord.
Let the heathen be wakened and come up
to the valley of Jehoshaphat, for there
will I sit to judge all the heathen
round about.
Now, letting you know that God's going
to come and he going to judge all the
nations and he going to deal with all of
them doing uh uh for what they did to
Israel. Skip down to verse 11 and go
ahead.
>> That that was that was verse 12. Verse
14, brother, go ahead.
>> Okay. Multitudes, multitudes in the
valley of decision. For the day of the
Lord is near in the valley of decision.
>> Go ahead.
>> The sun and the moon shall be darkened,
and the stars shall withdraw their
shining.
The Lord also shall roar out of Zion,
and utter his voice from Jerusalem, and
the heavens and the earth shall shake.
But the Lord will be the hope of his
people and the strength of the children
of Israel.
>> And that's when the Lord going to come
and he's going to take down all the
nations.
That's all that's talking about. That's
all I have to say.
>> All right. Sister Deborah, time check as
we take another question or two.
>> Yes. Uh the time is 8:56,
so I think Valencia will be the last
one.
Uh she states she wants you to explain
Romans 14 verse4.
>> So she wants some explanations on Roman
14 and verse 14.
>> 14. Yes.
>> All right. Why don't we go there and
read that, brother?
>> Romans 14 and 14. All right.
It says, "I know and am persuaded by the
Lord Jesus that there is nothing unclean
of itself, but to him that esteemth
anything to be unclean, to him it is
unclean."
>> Open to the panel.
>> And which and which it is. So, you know,
like like people go there to try and get
around the dietary laws,
>> right?
>> So, so nothing is unclean unto itself,
but he that extend
a thing unclean to him is a is unclean.
Right.
>> Yeah.
>> So, le esteem unclean animals is
unclean. I think there's Exodus the uh
uh Leviticus the 20th chapter. Leviticus
the 11th chapter.
>> Uh the I know 11th chapter tell you
about the dietary law but I want to go
and Leviticus
>> looking at 20 and 22 or 25.
>> Yeah. Think up at 20 25 and 26.
>> Okay.
>> Okay. Leviticus.
What is that? 20 25 and 26.
>> Yes.
>> Yeah. 24 would 24 would be a good pickup
where where the Lord say he separated us
from other people.
>> Oh yeah.
>> So So started at 25 24. Okay.
>> It says, "But I have said unto you, ye
shall inherit their land, and I will
give it unto you to possess it, a land
that flowth with milk and honey. I am
the Lord your God, which have separated
you from other people.
>> Ye shall therefore put difference
between clean beasts and unclean, and
between unclean fouls and clean, and ye
shall not make your souls abominable by
beast, or by foul, or by any manner of
living thing that creepeth on the
ground, which I have separated from you
as unclean.
So who esteemed him as unclean?
>> God did.
>> The Lord did.
>> So if a thing is unclean to God, then is
unclean to everybody.
>> That's right.
>> That's what what it's saying there. To
him that extem a thing unclean to him is
unclean. To the one that extean
uh h beast is the Lord.
And I think he overrides everybody else.
That's all
>> every time. Every time.
All right, Sister Deborah, one more
question and we'll call it.
>> Um, well, it's 9:00.
>> It's nine. Okay. Well, let's call it
nine then.
>> Yes.
>> All right, we'll do that. So, we want to
thank everybody from all around the
world who sent in those questions and we
took joy in answering them for you. And
we like to say that if you submitted a
question and we have a chance to get to
it that um no resubmit it sister Deborah
take it put it in rotation and we will
deal with that question next week. So
until we all come together again we ask
you to please be safe be blessed stay
prayed up and may the Lord have mercy on
us all as brother James closes us out.
Our Father, which art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name. Thy kingdom come,
thy will be done, in earth as it is in
heaven. Give us this day our daily
bread, and forgive us our debts as we
forgive our debtors, and lead us not
into temptation, but deliver us from
evil. For thine is the kingdom, and the
power, and the glory forever. in Jesus
name we pray. Amen.